import { Question } from "../components/MovieQuiz";

export const dotsData: Question[] = [
  {
    question: "What is the profession of Yoo Si-jin, the main male character?",
    options: ["Soldier", "Doctor", "Journalist", "Engineer"],
    answer: "Soldier",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of the special forces unit led by Yoo Si-jin?",
    options: ["Alpha Team", "Bravo Squad", "Delta Force", "Gamma Unit"],
    answer: "Alpha Team",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the name of the fictional country where much of the drama takes place?",
    options: ["Urk", "Iraq", "Malgoria", "Agriya"],
    answer: "Urk",
  },
  {
    question: "Who is Kang Mo-yeon?",
    options: ["A doctor", "A soldier", "A journalist", "A teacher"],
    answer: "A doctor",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What event brings Yoo Si-jin and Kang Mo-yeon back together after their initial separation?",
    options: [
      "A medical mission",
      "A charity event",
      "A peace summit",
      "A training exercise",
    ],
    answer: "A medical mission",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What natural disaster strikes the fictional country of Urk during the series?",
    options: ["Earthquake", "Flood", "Tsunami", "Hurricane"],
    answer: "Earthquake",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of the second lead couple in the drama?",
    options: [
      "Seo Dae-young and Yoon Myung-ju",
      "Yoo Si-jin and Kang Mo-yeon",
      "Kim Ji-hoon and Park Hye-soo",
      "Lee Chi-hoon and Ha Ja-ae",
    ],
    answer: "Seo Dae-young and Yoon Myung-ju",
  },
  {
    question: "Who is the commander of the medical team in Urk?",
    options: [
      "Doctor Song Sang-hyun",
      "Doctor Kang Mo-yeon",
      "Doctor Ha Ja-ae",
      "Doctor Lee Chi-hoon",
    ],
    answer: "Doctor Kang Mo-yeon",
  },
  {
    question: "What item does Yoo Si-jin use to propose to Kang Mo-yeon?",
    options: ["A diamond ring", "A necklace", "A scarf", "A watch"],
    answer: "A diamond ring",
  },
  {
    question: "What nickname does Yoo Si-jin frequently use for Kang Mo-yeon?",
    options: ["Beauty", "Doctor", "Ace", "Boss"],
    answer: "Beauty",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What promise does Yoo Si-jin make to Kang Mo-yeon at the end of the series?",
    options: [
      "To stay by her side",
      "To quit the military",
      "To move to Urk",
      "To start a family",
    ],
    answer: "To stay by her side",
  },
];
